{
    "subject": "resource/Frederick_Valentine_Melsheimer",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Duchy_of_Brunswick",
    "human_readable": "Frederick Valentine Melsheimer was born in the Duchy of Brunswick.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9427056908607483,
            "question": "Where was Frederick Valentine Melsheimer born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8877353072166443,
            "question": "What was the name of the region where Frederick Valentine Melsheimer was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8688474893569946,
            "question": "Were there any notable events happening in the Duchy of Brunswick during Frederick Valentine Melsheimer's time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7600938677787781,
            "question": "When do historical records indicate Frederick Valentine Melsheimer was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6940072178840637,
            "question": "What other historical figures were born in the Duchy of Brunswick?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5476811528205872,
            "question": "How might Frederick Valentine Melsheimer's birthplace have influenced his life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4803427755832672,
            "question": "Are there any famous people associated with the Duchy of Brunswick?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44237563014030457,
            "question": "What might we learn about Frederick Valentine Melsheimer's life from knowing his birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42890262603759766,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the Duchy of Brunswick?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11484910547733307,
            "question": "What is the significance of the location where someone is born?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Frederick Valentine Melsheimer was born in the Duchy of Brunswick.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5225_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the Duchy of Brunswick?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5225_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What might we learn about Frederick Valentine Melsheimer's life from knowing his birthplace?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5225_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous people associated with the Duchy of Brunswick?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5225_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5225_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5225_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5225_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5225_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5225_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5225_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5225_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5225_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5225_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5225_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples to evaluate! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for the answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about Frederick Valentine Melsheimer, including his birth place as Negenborn, which is part of the Duchy of Brunswick. Therefore, the statement that Frederick Valentine Melsheimer was born in the Duchy of Brunswick is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}